[{"answer": "Well, you know, right now, I don't think that there is.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 42, "question": "Is there any credence talking about this stage, do you think?", "qSentId": 41}, {"answer": "Oh, I think absolutely.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 76, "question": "Bob, from everything you just heard there from Ronald Kessler, does this make sense to you that this could be the sequence of events?", "qSentId": 75}, {"answer": "Yes, that exactly what happened.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 93, "question": "To me, one of the key questions here is when did the White House get ahold of this investigation, and did they make a conscious decision for this not to be released to the media until after the election?", "qSentId": 92}, {"answer": "Well, a lot of things don't ring true, and that's why, you know, we're going to need some time, although we'd love to have all the answers right now because that's how we are.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 104, "question": "It doesn't ring true, does it?", "qSentId": 103}, {"answer": "It's virtually not.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 183, "question": "I mean, it's hard to construct a massive security breach, isn't it?", "qSentId": 182}, {"answer": "It's Suzanne, I'm sorry.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 193, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 192}, {"answer": "No, no, no.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 219, "question": "Bob, if you don't agree, why?", "qSentId": 218}, {"answer": "REMER: Yes, of course, I am.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 264, "question": "Are you shocked, as everybody else, by these revelations today?", "qSentId": 263}, {"answer": "Well, I don't think you can ever know in an affair like this how it came about.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 270, "question": "What do you think would have caused him to behave like this given he's always stood for the complete opposite?", "qSentId": 269}, {"answer": "Well, that would be serious, but I would be surprised if that were the case.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 274, "question": "And if it turns out that the FBI investigation was kept quiet by the White House until after the election, what would be the political ramifications of that?", "qSentId": 273}, {"answer": "It could be quite serious, I agree.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 295, "question": "How do we get the CIA back on track?", "qSentId": 294}, {"answer": "Well, I doubt that.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Could it be that he's fallen on his sword over an affair to protect a wider scandal?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "I'm doing great.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "I'm doing fine.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 325, "question": "How are you?", "qSentId": 324}, {"answer": "Well, it's very disturbing to be in a position like the director of the Central Intelligence Agency.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "What do you feel about what's happened?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, this is a man who has an incredible amount of knowledge and secrets and information that we don't want others to find out about.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "What would you say to that in his particular case?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "There has to be some sort of agreement worked out.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 342, "question": "Is there the will amongst senior Republicans to do business, do you think?", "qSentId": 341}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 357, "question": "Do you plead guilty?", "qSentId": 356}, {"answer": "I don't intend to do anything right now other than spend a little time working to make sure that we don't walk away from the very principles that made our country great, and that there is at least one party that's going to stand by those founding principles.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 384, "question": "Do you intend on running again?", "qSentId": 383}, {"answer": "Well, I think the president needs to face the fact that the American people went to the polls and elected a House of Representatives committed to not raising taxes.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 411, "question": "Isn't it the sensible thing now for you to withdraw this utterly implacable position, no tax increases for the history of America ever again?", "qSentId": 410}, {"answer": "Well, of course, as you know, if you take the Buffett rule tax that the president has endorsed, raising taxes on people making a million dollars, that raises 48 billion dollars over a decade, which is less than half of one percent of the president's deficit spending.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 423, "question": "And shouldn't the wealthy just bump a few more dollars in?", "qSentId": 422}, {"answer": "I think a deal does have to get done eventually, Piers.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 431, "question": "Do you see enough positivity in the rhetoric that a deal can get done here?", "qSentId": 430}, {"answer": "One of the problems, of course, if you do raise taxes, is a lot of Americans who would then be brought into that bracket are small business owners.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "Or do they think that it is appropriate to have the rich bear the lion's share of deficit reduction and the responsibility for reducing deficits by means of generating more revenues?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Your party lost.", "docId": "121109pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "Final word?", "qSentId": 472}]